<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PassCSE</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tab_1">WELCOME!</string>
    <string name="tab_2">INTERACTIVE QUIZ</string> <!-- Corrected "INTERECTIVE" to "INTERACTIVE" -->
    <string name="tab_3">LET’S BEGIN!</string>

    <string name="Intro_Text">Prepare for your Civil Service Exam with ease. Choose your exam level, take timed assessments, and improve your skills with each retake.</string>
    <string name="Second_Text">Every assessment offers new randomized questions to help you master the material.</string>
    <string name="Third_Text">Good luck, and let’s get started on your journey to success!</string>

    <string name="avatar_description">Avatar image representing user selection</string>

    <string name="ABOUT_THE_APP">The PassCSE app is your ultimate companion on the journey to acing the Civil Service Examination.
        Designed for both <b>Professional</b> and <b>Sub-Professional</b> aspirants, this comprehensive mobile platform provides everything you need to prepare effectively and confidently.
        With user-friendly features and a wealth of resources tailored to critical exam topics such as <b>Analytical Ability</b>, <b>Numerical Ability</b>, <b>Verbal Ability</b>, and <b>Clerical Ability</b>,
        PassCSE empowers you to conquer your study goals.<b>\nThis application simulates the Civil Service Exam for practice purposes only and does not guarantee success in the actual exam</b>.</string>

    <string name="objectiveTXT"><b>Empowering Success in Civil Service Examinations</b>. At PassCSE, our goal is to support you in succeeding in the Civil Service Examination.
        We recognize the challenges involved in exam preparation, and we\'re here to make it easier.
        Our app offers targeted content reviews and realistic timed assessments to help you build knowledge and confidence.
        Whether you\'re focusing on Professional or Sub-Professional subjects, PassCSE is designed to provide a personalized learning experience that meets your study needs.</string>

    <string name="developers_info"> <b>BS- INFORMATION SYSTEMS - 2A</b></string>
    <string name="Names">
        <b>BALCE, IAN JAY M.</b>            \nianjaybalce1994@gmail.com\n
        \n <b>FRANCISCO, DEN-MARK C.</b>    \nfdenmark076@gmail.com\n
        \n <b>GAN, JONARD O.</b>            \nganjonard3@gmail.com\n
        \n <b>JANE, JOHN KENNETH A.</b>     \nkennethjane670@gmail.com

    </string>
</resources>
